

# PEDRO GABRIEL CAIRES

Fullstack Web Developer

# **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

Hello world! My name is Pedro Gabriel and I'm a Fullstack dev with specialization in PHP/Laravel

# **MY STORY**

I started programming when I was 16, I've always been a hardware and software lover, when I started to attend the Technician School in Computer Science it was a big definitive push into the area. In 2020, along with two long time friends, I created Phog Tech, a freelance team specialized in Web solutions. After that I participated in several Open Source projects and now I currently work at I'M Labs, a company of diverse technological solutions. I stand out for my agility with new technologies and the ease of solving problems.

#### **SKILLS**

- PHP (Laravel, Lumen, Symphony & others)
  - Javascript (Node.js, Vue.js, React.js)
- MySQL (and other relational databases)
  - Semantic HTML, CSS, CSS/SASS
    - Python
    - Java
    - React Native
      - Docker
  - AWS (and other cloud solutions)
    - Intermediate English

## **EDUCATION**

- "Curso Técnico em Informática" at Eniac College (2019~2021)
- College in Information Systems at FIAP (2022~Present)

## CONTACT

Cell Phone: +55 11 986341150 Email: pedrogcs0104@gmail.com

# LINKS

**GITHUB:** https://github.com/dgtyPedro

**LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/pedro-gabriel-caires/

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **PHOG TECH**

# PHP Back-End Developer (2020~2021)

I was responsible for structuring and developing all database part of the projects that the team was hired. During this period I learned a lot about PHP as a language itself and how MySQL databases worked.

#### I'M LABS

#### Fullstack Developer (2021~Present)

An excellent opportunity in which I was exposed to several new and different technologies, I could test a little bit of everything and it was the period that I am learning the most in my life. I made several projects with ViteJs, Next, Laravel/Jetstream and other technologies. In the last few months I have been working mostly with Laravel, which has become my main technology.

# **NOTABLE PROJECTS**

**- Lotopower:** Lottery tips and simulations platform, made 100% by me in Laravel. LINK: <a href="https://lotopower.com.br">https://lotopower.com.br</a>

- **dumpi-fy**: Spotify playlist manager made in PHP.

LINK: <a href="https://github.com/dgtyPedro/dumpi-fy">https://github.com/dgtyPedro/dumpi-fy</a>

- **Geek Horror:** Horror Quizz site, I did the backend in PHP.

LINK: <a href="https://geekhorror.com.br">https://geekhorror.com.br</a>

- AdaWendy: SPA made 100% by me in React for the company AdaWendy.

LINK: <a href="https://www.adawendy.com.br">https://www.adawendy.com.br</a>